Hey.
Hey, uh, Mon, I saw the
Porsche parked out front.
Can I get the keys?
I thought I'd take that bad boy
out for a little spin.
Wait, you let Ross
drive the Porsche?
And when I ask, you say
you're the only one
who's allowed to drive it.
Yeah, well, he's my brother.
And plus, he drives so slow,
he could never hurt it.
It's a car, Monica,
not a rocket ship.
Whatever, Ross.
Just replace the bulbs
in the brake lights
after you're done.
Hey.
Hi.
Saw the Porsche out there, Mon.
Looking good.
When do I get to take
that baby out again?
You let Joey drive it?
I've never driven it, okay?
Not once.
Okay, once.
Okay, I drive it all the time.
Nice work, everybody.
So much for the "you can drive
it, but don't tell Rachel" plan.
Wow.
Can't believe you lied to me.
Okay, I can fix this.
Okay, Monica, Rachel thinks
all you can talk about
is the wedding.
Really?
Well, Rachel, the reason I won't
let you drive the Porsche
is because
you're a terrible driver.
There, that wasn't
about the wedding.
Look, Rach, if you
want to go for a ride
in the Porsche
I'll be glad to take you for
a quick spin around the block.
Yeah, you got a couple hours?
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Whoo!
That was a brisk ride.
Take the top down, did you?
Only way to fly.
Come on, Ross,
give me the keys.
Monica does not know
what she's talking about.
I'm an excellent driver.
You're fast and
irresponsible.
That adds up
to a bad driver.
Well, in high school, that
added up to head cheerleader.
Did you see the look
that girl just gave me?
Huh?
She must've seen me
cruisin' in the bad boy.
I think she's checking out
your beehive, Ross.
What?
Give me a brush.
Give me the keys.
No way.
Well, no brush.
Fine.
You know what?
It doesn't matter.
Because, if I
remember correctly
there is a comb on the
floor of the bathroom.
Alimony.
Chandler, we still haven't
gotten an RSVP from your dad.
Oh, right.
Um... maybe that's because
I didn't send him an invitation.
Chandler, he's your father.
He should be at your wedding.
I don't even know the man, okay?
We're not that close.
I haven't seen him in years.
What are you going to do
when he finds out
he wasn't asked?
He doesn't have to know.
It's not like we run
in the same circles.
I hang out with you guys
and he... stars
in a drag show in Vegas.
Ooh, I think I want
to trade circles.
Look, trust me, you don't want
him there, either, okay?
Nobody's going to be
staring at the bride
when the father of the groom
is wearing a backless dress.
So what?
As long as he's not wearing
a white dress and a veil
I don't care.
Okay, I think I need
to do some shopping.
Ah.
Ooh, nice.
Aah!
My, God!
What do you think you're doing?
Just washing the windshield.
Ow!
There is no way
I am letting you
drive this car.
So why don't you just
hand over the keys?
Oh. Hmm.
Wha... ah-ah-ah,
do-do not start this car.
( engine starts )
Okay, okay.
I will give you 20 bucks
if you get out of this car
right now.
Look, Ross,
if you're so freaked out
just get in the car.
With you? Yeah, right.
All right.
Okay, okay, okay.
What are you doing?
Get in the front.
In the death seat?!
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Hey, sweetie.
Ready to go?
Yeah, sure.
Ooh, I left my purse
up at Monica's.
I'll be right back.
Wait a minute.
What?
Oh.
Ooh.
( giggles )
Whoa, that one
kept going.
So, you and Phoebe, huh?
How long you been going out?
Over a month.
Wow.
Maybe you and I ought to get to
know each other a little better.
Sure, I'd like that.
Yeah.
So, uh...
what's your name?
It's Jake.
Joey.
Hey, Jake, do you
like the Knicks?
Yeah. Big fan.
Me, too.
There's a game on Tuesday.
You want to go?
Yeah, that'd be great.
Let me make sure
I'm not doing
anything Tuesday.
Here.
What's this?
It's your suitcase.
We're going to Las Vegas.
Are you serious?
Mm-hmm.
You mean, like, eloping?
No more stupid wedding stuff?
No more "these flowers or these
flowers or these flowers?"
Think of the money
we'll save.
We're not eloping.
I love the flowers.
Can our wedding
be bigger, please?
We're going to Las Vegas
to see your dad.
It's time you two talked
and I want to get to
know my father-in-law.
We already went over this,
and I won.
No, you didn't.
Oh, and, honey,
just so you know
now that you're
marrying me
you don't get
to win anymore.
Look, forget it, okay?
I don't want to go.
I don't want to see him.
I don't want to.
Chandler, look, I know that
your dad embarrassed you.
I know...
No, no, no.
All kids are embarrassed
by their parents.
You'd have to come up
with a whole new word
for what I went through.
When I was
in high school
he used to come to all
of my swim meets
dressed as a different
Hollywood starlet.
You know,
it's hard enough to be 14.
You're skinny,
you're wearing Speedos
that your mom promised
you would grow into.
And you look up into the stands,
and there's your dad
cheering you on
dressed as Carmen Miranda.
He's wearing a headdress
with real fruit
that he will later hand out to
your friends as a healthy snack.
Hey, look, the point is
that he was at every
one of your swim meets
and he was there
cheering you on.
Okay, that's
a pretty great dad.
He had sex
with Mr. Garibaldi.
Who's Mr. Garibaldi?
Does it matter?
Look, Chandler...
you're not
14 anymore, okay?
Maybe it's time that
you let that stuff go.
If your father's not
at your wedding
you're going to regret it
for the rest of your life.
Yeah, o-okay.
But I'm just
doing this for you.
Yes!
So I really never
get to win anymore?
How much did you ever
really win before?
Hey, Pheebs.
Hey.
Listen, you know how, uh
when you're wearing pants
and you lean forward
I check out your underwear?
Yeah.
Well, when Jake did it,
I saw that...
he was wearing
women's underwear.
I know-- they were mine.
Oh...
( chuckles )
No, no, wait,
that's weird.
No, it's not.
We were just goofing around
and I dared him
to try them on.
That's weird.
I'm wearing his briefs
right now.
That's... kind of hot.
I think so, too.
And that little flap?
Great for holding
my lipstick.
Yeah, I wouldn't know
about that.
And you know, Jake says
that women's underwear is
actually more comfortable.
And he loves the way the silk
feels against his skin.
Well, next thing you know
he'll be telling you that
your high heels are
good for his posture.
There is nothing wrong
with Jake, okay?
He is all man.
I'm thinking
even more than you.
Oh, yeah, he looked
like a real lumberjack
in those pink lacies.
I'm just saying
that only a man
completely secure
with his masculinity
could walk around
in women's underwear.
I don't think you
could ever do that.
Hey, I am secure
with my masculinity.
Okay, whatever.
You've seen my huge
stack of porn, right?
God, I forgot how much
I love driving.
I have got to get
my license renewed.
You don't have a valid
driver's license?
Okay, that is it.
Pull over right now.
Oh, Ross,
you're so tense.
You've just
got to relax.
Okay?
Just need to relax,
all right?
You just need to relax.
Wh-What are you cra...
Okay, that's not funny.
Just stop horsing around.
I am not horsing
around, okay?
I am "Porsche-ing"
around.
( police siren wailing )
Uh-oh.
Okay, stay calm.
Nothing's going
to happen to you.
You are not
in that much trouble.
Really? You think so?
I was talking to myself.
You're going down.
Nah.
Has someone taken
your order yet?
Oh, yeah, uh, she did.
Uh, he did.
She?
I-I'm sorry, I'm new.
I don't...
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I just ordered a beer.
You're straight-- I get it.
I still say that if
we had called your dad
we could've gotten
better seats.
No, no
I don't want him to know
we're here yet.
I'm not sure
if I'm ready for that.
And besides, he's not
going to be too happy
to see me, either.
Why not?
Well, I don't know
if I've told you this
but he's kind of tried
to get in contact with me
a lot over
the last few years.
What?
Yeah
he's made phone calls,
written letters
even came to New York.
But I always said I was
too busy to see him.
It's all very
"Cat's in the Cradle."
I don't want to get into it.
Here we go.
( piano plays chord )
Hello, darlings.
And there's Daddy.
Okay, switch
places with me.
Switch places with me!
I'll go under,
you go over.
Yeah, I'll get
right on that.
Come on, Ross!
No, hey, Rach...
Come on.
Yeah, I'm sure
we won't get arrested
for this.
Hi, Officer. Was I going
a little too fast?
Oh, my God.
Can I see your
license, please?
Oh, yes, absolutely.
You know, it's weird
but, uh, I had
a dream last night
that I was stopped
by a policeman.
And then, he,
um, well...
I probably shouldn't
tell you the rest.
Your license.
( clearing throat ):
Yes. Here you go.
Officer, uh... Handsome.
It's Hanson.
Oops, sorry. My mistake.
Dear Lord.
Wow.
Here it comes.
This is a great picture.
Oh!
Really, you think so?
You know, I had just
rolled right out of bed.
Well, you look
phenomenal.
Well, she should-- it
was taken ten years ago.
You know what?
You're-you're probably, um...
probably wondering about
the old date on there.
Yes, I am.
You're an Aquarius, huh?
I bet you're a Gemini.
Nope.
Taurus?
Virgo?
Nope.
Sagittarius?
Yep.
I knew it!
Well, I'll tell
you what.
Yeah?
You won't speed anymore?
I won't speed.
And you promise
you'll take
care of this?
I promise.
In the meantime,
let him drive.
He have a license?
Yeah.
Can he handle a stick?
Uh, well...
I can handle a stick!
♪ I feel pretty ♪
♪ Oh, so pretty ♪
♪ I feel pretty and witty
and... ♪
ALL:
♪ Gay! ♪
Wait, that can't
be your father.
Believe me, I've been
saying that for years.
Oh, my God.
What?
That's Mr. Garibaldi
playing the piano.
♪ For I'm loved by a pretty ♪
♪ Wonderful boy. ♪
( applause and hooting )
Hello, and welcome
to the show.
I see some of our regulars
in the audience.
And a couple of irregulars.
( laughter )
He's coming
into the audience.
He's coming into
the audience.
Relax, you'll be fine.
Ooh, much better.
You're invisible now.
And where are you from?
Bakersfield.
I'm sorry?
No, no, I heard.
I'm just sorry.
It can't happen
like this, okay?
I'll meet you back
at the hotel.
Oh, look, a standing ovation
already, so early in the show.
Oh, turn around, darling.
Let me see your pretty face.
Can we have our drinks, please?
Uh, waiter... uh, -tress.
Hey, Pheebs.
Hey.
Check it out.
Huh?
How much of a man am I?
Wow, nice.
Manly and also
kind of a slut.
You know, I'm beginning to see
what Jake was talking about.
Uh-huh.
The silk feels really good.
Yeah.
And-and things aren't
as smashed down
as I thought they
were going to be.
That's great, Joe.
Yeah, and you have
so many more choices
than you do
with men's underwear.
Bikini, French cut, thong.
And the fabrics-- you got
cotton, silk, lace.
And you know what
I've always wondered about?
Pantyhose.
You know, the way
they start at your toe
and then they go
all the way up to...
I should go take these off,
shouldn't I?
I think it's important
that you do.
Mmm.
So, what's your name?
Chandler.
HELENA:
What an unusual name.
You must've had terribly
fascinating parents.
Oh, they're a hoot.
And who is your friend?
I'm-I'm Monica.
Monica.
Where are you from?
New York.
I'm not very fond of New York.
Queens, I like.
Ooh, what is this
sparkling something,
honey, huh?
( ooh-ing and ah-ing )
Actually, Monica and I
are engaged.
Really?
Congratulations.
When's the big day?
In-in two weeks.
I see.
Well, I wish you both a lifetime
of happiness.
So, you're bald.
Wait, wait.
We'd really love it
if you could be there.
Really?
I know it would make me happy...
Ma'am.
Then I wouldn't miss it
for the world.
Oh, I'm getting all misty here.
You'd think I was having
my legs waxed or something.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Thanks for making me
do this.
Before we go on
with the show
I just want to say
to the bride and groom
how lucky they are
to have found each other.
Into every life
a little rain must fall.
Fortunately, in my life...
♪ It's raining men ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ Hallelujah... ♪
When I was growing up
I played the one
on the far left.
♪ It's raining men ♪
♪ Amen... ♪
You know what?
Remind me to introduce
you to someone.
Who?
Fourth gear.
( siren blaring )
What?!
What does he want?
I wasn't doing anything.
Well, maybe he saw
your hand slip briefly
from the ten
and two o'clock position.
Maybe it's, uh,
Sergeant Sagittarius
coming back to flirt
some more.
It's a different guy.
Good evening,
Officer.
Do you know how fast
you were traveling
back there?
Uh, no, I don't, but
it could not have
been more than 60.
You're right. It was 37.
I mean, you're not going
to give me a ticket
for driving too slow,
are you?
That's right.
You know, Officer
I, uh, I had the weirdest
dream last night.
Oh, my God.
Your license, please?
You don't... you don't want
to hear about my dream...
Officer Pretty?
It's Petty.
I'll be right back
with your ticket.
You have a son.
I know. I know.
Feel better?
Yeah, much.
Listen, uh
not that I'm insecure
about my manhood
or anything, you know.
But, uh, I think I need
to hook up with a woman,
like, right now.
Yeah, I understand.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey. Hi.
Hi.
You look familiar.
Do I know you
from somewhere?
I don't think so.
Oh, maybe it's because
I'm on television.
I'm an actor
on Days of Our Lives.
Wow.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
$4.50, please.
Oh, let me get this.
These are for you.